Hello, in this video I will tell you
how you can show self-respect through this Swaraj
and you can continue with the one which is available in Play Store.
After taking the photo first
select on satisfaction back customer and
enter the location of the vehicle and continue. Now your
proposal will be saved on my transaction,
go there and you
can see the inspection ID of the proposal and
after commenting you will get the payment release here.
Now launch the installed app,
select on the bottom turn on it and
enter the vehicle number on mobile satisfaction.
You can check that all the details of the vehicle are
showing here. On starting you will get the
camera option. First of all
cut out the registration number of the vehicle and take a photo
and after that take a photo of the vehicle from the front side
and after that take a photo of the vehicle from the right side of the front
work prohibition.
You can take this photo in any hotel and
take a photo from the back side by calling.
Now if you are not able to see the car effect
in the camera then you
can do it on Amrit landscape mode or you can take a little behind your
photo and keep in mind that the photo of the vehicle should be
visible in your  It should be there,
after this turn on the engine of the car,
take a photo of the meter, keep in mind that the meter should
not be at zero, the engine should be on,
there is a
photo of the chassis number,
in Maruti the chassis number is
near the door, in different models you will
also find it near the font, after this
take the reading of the potometer on which the kilometer total
is shown, now submit it, after submitting this,
you will get approval for Rs. 3241,
after which you can now make the policy by making the payment,
thank you